{
    "id": "asano",
    "name": "浅野充利",
    "yomi": "Mitsutoshi Asano",
    "text": [
        "名古屋在住のサラリーマンです。座右の銘は｢コンクリートから芝へ｣です。",
        "I work in Nagoya. My motto/policy is to grass from concrete"
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Which do you like?",
            "jp": "どっちが好き？",
            "yes": "beach",
            "left": "砂浜",
            "no": "lawn",
            "right": "芝生"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "Where do you want to day dreaming?",
            "jp": "ぼーっとするなら？",
            "yes": "indoor",
            "left": "屋内",
            "no": "outdoor",
            "right": "屋外"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "What do you imagine with sunshine?",
            "jp": "日光浴のイメージは？",
            "yes": "cuddle hormon",
            "left": "幸せホルモン",
            "no": "freckle",
            "right": "シミ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "Which do you want once a day?",
            "jp": "１日１回ほしいものは何？",
            "yes": "imagination",
            "left": "イマジネーション",
            "no": "motivation",
            "right": "モチベーション"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "What do you think about doing nothing?",
            "jp": "何もしない、何も考えない事は？",
            "yes": "easy peasy",
            "left": "楽チン",
            "no": "need some courage",
            "right": "勇気がいる"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "You want to drink?",
            "jp": "飲むなら？",
            "yes": "beer",
            "left": "ビール",
            "no": "wine",
            "right": "ワイン"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Which is more helpful?",
            "jp": "役立つものは？",
            "yes": "books",
            "left": "本",
            "no": "friends",
            "right": "友達"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "Which do you need?",
            "jp": "必要なものは？",
            "yes": "being relax",
            "left": "安らぎ",
            "no": "being plentiful",
            "right": "豊かさ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "What is needed in town do you think?",
            "jp": "街には何が必要？",
            "yes": "green",
            "left": "グリーン",
            "no": "buildings",
            "right": "ビル"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "Which smell do you like?",
            "jp": "好きな香りは？",
            "yes": "smell of the ocean",
            "left": "磯の香り",
            "no": "smell of curry and fried noodle",
            "right": "カレー、焼そばの香り"
        }
    ]
}